surf4dollars.com 2016-05-08

# Surf4Dollars - Earn, Share, Get Traffic BETA

**Privacy Policy**

Welcome to the Surf4Dollars.com Service, a web service utility that connects employers and workers on a micro level. By using or accessing the Surf4Dollars.com Service, you agree that you have read, understand and are bound by these Terms of Use ("Terms"). We reserve the right, at our sole discretion, to change or delete portions of these Terms at any time without further notice. Your continued use of the Surf4Dollars.com Service after any such changes constitutes your acceptance of the new Terms.

**Surf4Dollars.com Principles**

We built Surf4Dollars.com to make it easy to create paid ads, generate traffic by browsing other websites. We understand you may not want everyone in the world to access your personal information; that is why all personal information is hidden from other users. Our privacy settings is very strict and does not allow other users to see any of your personal information except your Surf4Dollars.com Display Name.

Surf4Dollars.com does not share information with other users. As employer you choose what information you put in response to replying to a worker. As a worker you choose what information you put in response to replying to an employer. We suggest you not to reply with any personal information such as your MSN ID, Skype ID, Email, phone number, etc.. There is no need to publish any of your personal information as all communication in Surf4Dollars.com system is based upon user Display Name.

**Safe Use of Surf4Dollars.com**

In general Surf4Dollars.com is suitable for everyone but certain ads might not be acceptable for some people. If you are a child, below 21 years old or feel offended by adult material, please be aware sometimes bad users ay change links and you may see an offiensive ad. You should immediately report the ad using the report site button in the surf menu. If it is an offensive bookmark please use the support system to submit the URL of the site and the site name

**The Information We Collect**

When you visit Surf4Dollars.com you provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Web Site use information collected by us as you interact with our Web Site.

When you register with Surf4Dollars.com, you may provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.

When you enter Surf4Dollars.com, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Surf4Dollars.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login information so you don't have to login again when you come back to Surf4Dollars.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. If you don't want other people who use same computer to login to your Surf4Dollars.com account then you should always log out of your account after finishing with your activities.

Although you should never disclose your personal information to other users you communicate with, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot control the actions of other Users with whom you may choose to share information. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that information you post on the Site will not be viewed by unauthorized persons. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site. You understand and acknowledge that, even after removal or termination of your account, copies of User Content and your previous actions may remain viewable in cached and archived pages.

Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on Surf4Dollars.com is a violation of the Surf4Dollars.com Terms of Service and should be reported to us using Surf4Dollars.com' email published on the Site.

If you choose to use our invitation service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your friend's email address. We will send your friend an email or instant message in your name inviting him or her to visit the site, and may send up to two reminders to them. Surf4Dollars.com stores this information to send invitations and reminders, to register a friend connection if your invitation is accepted, to allow you to see invitations you have sent, and to track the success of our referral program. Your friend may contact us through the Contact us form on our Contact us or to Surf4Dollars.com' email published on the Site to request that we remove this information from our database.

Surf4Dollars.com may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, etc. in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.

By using Surf4Dollars.com, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States and EU countries.

**Children Under Age 13**

Surf4Dollars.com does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for Surf4Dollars.com or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Surf4Dollars.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us through the Contact us form or via Surf4Dollars.com' email which are both available on the Site.

**Children Between the Ages of 13 and 18**

We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.

Use of Information Obtained by Surf4Dollars.com

When you register with Surf4Dollars.com, you create your own account. Most of your profile information is not displayed to other users. Unless you decide to share your personal information with other users, the only information displayed is your accounts Display Name. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by Surf4Dollars.com that we think you may find valuable.

We will also use your cell phone number to send you a PIN code you need to enter to activate payments to you. This will only need to be done once on the initial withdrawal request.

Surf4Dollars.com may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if another users sends you a message regarding a job or a task, you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

Generally, you may opt out of such emails by changing notification settings under �Edit Profile � link, though Surf4Dollars.com reserves the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.

We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs, instant messaging services, Surf4Dollars.com Platform developers and other users of Surf4Dollars.com, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile.

Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

Surf4Dollars.com will not share information in your profile with third parties.

**Users data**

When you use Surf4Dollars.com certain information you post or share with other users, such as personal information, campaign data, task data, comments, messages, photos, videos or other information, may be shared with other users. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that when posting any information about a) campaigns or b) tasks to Surf4Dollars.com this information may become publicly available.

**Links**

Surf4Dollars.com may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site or to visit any website they find on Surf4Dollars.com to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Surf4Dollars.com.

**Third Party Advertising**

Advertisements that appear on Surf4Dollars.com are sometimes delivered (or "served") directly to users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Surf4Dollars.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Surf4Dollars.com unless you choose to share it with them.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Surf4Dollars.com and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

**Changing or Removing Information**

Surf4Dollars.com users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by sending an email to Surf4Dollars.com and request such action to be taken. Information will be updated if Surf4Dollars.com staff determines user did a mistake when submitting personal information, mail address, email or any other information submitted. Individuals who wish to deactivate their Surf4Dollars.com account may do so by contaction us and request account termination. We will terminate the account. Once account is terminated user will not be able to login and perform any actions otherwise available in Surf4Dollars.com system. Removed information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to other members of Surf4Dollars.com.

Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on Surf4Dollars.com, however, (e.g., sending a personal message to another Surf4Dollars.com user) or information that was shared by starting a campaign, submitting or rating a task you generally cannot remove such information.

**Security**

All data entered by our users (except some payment information) is saved on Surf4Dollars.com servers. Servers are based in United States operated by a hosting company. Hosting company should is responsible to update the server(s) with latest patches and prevent any possible attacks and prevent other people than those authorized by Surf4Dollars.com staff from accessing Surf4Dollars.com database.

Surf4Dollars.com takes appropriate precautions to protect our users' information. Your account information is located on a secured server behind a firewall. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number or your password), that information is always entered and processed at online payment system services such as Paypal or 2Checkout or others that are used to perform transactions. Before initiating payment to Surf4Dollars.com make sure to read Terms and Privacy policy at Paypal.com and 2Checkout.com.

Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information to us by email or instant messaging services. If you have any questions about the security of Surf4Dollars.com Web Site, please contact us through the Contact us form or via Surf4Dollars.com email published on the Site.

**Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**

Your use of Surf4Dollars.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including arbitration, limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use at any time. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately, and material changes will take effect within 30 days of their posting on this site. If we make changes, we will post them and will indicate at the top of this page the policy's new effective date. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or through notice on our home page. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us through the Contact us form or via Surf4Dollars.com email published on the Site.
